I'm sorry I scared you.
Who are you?
I wonder who I could be.
Why don't you guess?
Could you actually be...
Masamune?
Hey, it's been a while, Aki-chan.
I'm back.
#10 "The New School Term Filled With Doubts"
I was just about to go to sleep.
Now's not the time for that.
You wish to see the master of this house?
Yes! I have a letter from my grandfather.
Please take a look.
Pardon me.
"Adagaki Taigen promises the
15th-generation Gasou Kanetsugu
that your grandchild, the
17th-generation head, will..."
ma-ma... ma-mar...
Dad?
"That your grandchild, the 17th-generation
head, will marry into my family."
I am the 17th-generation Gasou Kanetsugu.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Calling
Makabe Masamune
No Service
Slide to Unlock
497,
498,
499...
500!
I see in your eyes...
The rising sun!
Rising sun!
Sun... Sun... Sun...
It's been so long! Did you
finish all your homework?
You've gotten so tan!
Adagaki Aki.
Please go out with me.
Why do men always feel so confident that
they're different from everyone else?
Huh? H-Hey!
Your Nipples Are Showing
What?!
Once again I have cut a worthless object.
Th-That's permanent marker!
Damn it! You'll regret this!
Well done, Aki-sama!
That was the ace of the baseball
team, wasn't it, Kikune-chan?
He was one pick away from
the Koushien, I think,
but he lost.
Wow, that's amazing.
But I'm stronger!
Much stronger.
Yeah, yeah. Well done, kendo club...
You may look up to me, Sonoka.
Nope. I'm two years older than you, Kikune.
Huh?!
I see that you two haven't changed.
You, too, Aki-sama!
Are you sure you should've rejected
the first one of the second term?
He almost made it to Koushien.
He already left the team, didn't he?
That means he's just a musclehead.
There it is! You're amazing, Aki-sama!
So cool!
Our Aki-sama...
From young to old...
Ruthlessly gives everyone a "No!"
Would you cut it out?
This happens all the time.
Is that really so?
Mari-chan!
It appears that lately you spend more time
with Makabe Masamune than
you do with us, Aki-sama.
Th... Th-Th-Th-That's not true!
I heard that you two spent
summer vacation together.
Th-That can't be!
I-Is that true, Aki-sama?
That was, um... Makabe didn't
leave me much choice.
I was trying to invite Shuri-kun, and...
Shuri Kojuurou
is also biologically a man.
Well, I mean...
If you have reconverted, Aki-sama,
then I'll just have to...
Um, uh...
Huh?
No, it's nothing.
I wanted to see Aki-sama in a swimsuit.
And at the ocean!
Not to mention, it was a private beach.
Wow, that's nice. A private beach.
I didn't know you had one.
Take me there sometime.
What a stupid man.
How dare you feign such closeness?
You'll just be cut down by Aki-sama again.
It'll be the second one, on the
first morning of the second term.
W-Well... I guess I wouldn't
be against considering it.
Really? That's great.
That's a promise, Aki-chan.
L-Let's hurry up and go. You still have
your transfer paperwork, don't you?
Yeah. Will you show me the way?
Of course.
Aki-sama...
Aki-sama, who would never acknowledge
even a celebrity or a soccer player...
Aki-sama, who gave a Tokyo University
student the name "Dried Whitebait"....
I can't believe it.
Girls, perhaps we had the
wrong idea this whole time.
What do you mean?
Perhaps Aki-sama wasn't the Cruel Princess
who tore apart one guy after another.
She wasn't?
But might actually be a
chubby-chaser instead.
I'm a hot guy! Thin yet macho!
Morning!
Good morning, Makabe-kun.
It's been a while.
Good morning.
Yup, good morning.
Why are you here?!
Because I am a student at
this school, Masamune-sama.
Didn't you go overseas to have surgery?
Yes.
So they sliced me up, yanked something out,
sewed me back up, and I came back.
That's graphic!
I stayed in the hospital
over there for a month,
but I was safely able to return yesterday.
Oh, I see.
A month?! Is that even possible?!
I was so troubled that whole time!
And how were you, Masamune-sama?
You spoke out so strongly the last time,
and you've had a month's time.
How much closer were you
able to get to Aki-sama?
U-Um, well...
Tra...
"Tra"?
I was training a bit.
Which means...
You haven't gotten anywhere?
I-I couldn't help it! I was thinking
about what you said the whole time!
You shouldn't throw around
pick-up lines so cheaply.
I-I'm not... That's not my intent!
See?
If you wait too long, your chance will
be taken from under your nose.
A guy?!
Come on, Fujinomiya-san.
You aren't implying that a tubby
like that could rival me, are you?
Did you lose even more weight?
I'd prefer that you said I toned up.
Indeed. I might just be imagining things.
Right?
Makabe-kun, let's walk home together.
Go on ahead of me.
I'm going to go give Adagaki-san
a gift from the country.
Shinshuu Soba
Muscle, muscle, excite, excite...
Okay.
I'm a different Masamune now.
I'm going to show her
just how much I've grown.
Good afternoon!
It's the hot guy from the
genus Hominidae, class Homo.
This is perfect for you right now.
I got you some 100% stone-milled
buckwheat flour from Shinshuu,
Adagaki-sa—
Someone's here, Aki-chan.
"Aki-chan"? Did he just say "Aki-chan"?!
Oh, Makabe.
Oh! Adagaki-san? Who might that person be?
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Gasou Kanetsugu. I transferred
to Yasaka High School today.
You're a transfer student?
Yup. Who are you?
Makabe Masamune.
Masamune, eh? What a coincidence.
My nickname is actually Masamune.
Hey, Aki-chan. It'd be confusing
to call me "Masamune" here,
so maybe you shouldn't.
If that's what you want.
Okay, it's settled.
Are you two acquaintances?
Are you a relative of Adagaki-san's?
Yeah. Well, rather than an acquaintance...
I'm her betrothed.
Betrothed
Betrothed?!
What?!
Right now, I'm a guest at Aki-chan's house.
Huh? Makabe-kun?
Pig's Foot, calm down.
H-How the hell am I supposed to stay calm?!
What does he mean by "betrothed"?!
It's just as it sounds.
Nobody told me about this!
Well, I couldn't get through to your cell phone.
Damn it! I guess there was no
reception in the mountains!
But I'm surprised, too.
I-Is there a possibility that he's lying?
I ran a signature analysis,
and apparently the letter is real.
So right now he's a guest at the mansion.
They're living together?!
Is this a light novel?! Or a dating sim?
Is this some exciting shoujo manga?!
B-But there's no way the Cruel
Princess who hates men so much
could stay quiet about this
whole "betrothed" thing!
That's what I thought, too, but...
What? That's not true?!
Aki-sama is acting strange.
Or maybe not strange, but...
It's love?
Huh?!
You can't be serious!
Who the hell is that guy?
It went your way!
Run! Run!
Gasou Kanetsugu.
160 centimeters tall. Somewhat short.
Estimated weight: 63 kilograms. Somewhat fat.
Wow!
Not bad, Kanetsugu-kun!
He's round but fast.
Thanks!
Despite having a short and fat
physique, he's pretty good at sports.
Using this formula here is simpler
and easier to understand.
Thanks, Gasou-kun!
I love math, so you can
ask me about it anytime.
Really? That's a huge help!
He's pretty smart, but has
a good attitude about it.
Are you looking for a seat?
There's a seat here!
Someone so friendly that he blends
in with both guys and girls.
Thanks!
But the biggest problem is...
Aki-chan! Let's eat together.
N-Not so loud.
Th-That bastard...
What the hell is going on?
Apparently Aki-sama met him in the past.
Yeah, but his belly is
sitting on top of his belt!
She was totally ruthless with me about that!
Did she consume so many calories
that her brain just short-circuited?
I don't think so.
Then what the hell is that?
A girl's heart is like the autumn... something.
I can't accept this!
I'm sorry, Pig's Foot.
No, you don't need to apologize, Master.
You can say that, but...
What the heck?
Mari-chan.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's fine. We weren't talking
about anything important.
I'm just in too much shock. That Aki-sama...
She was always full of mysteries.
She never ate lunch with us even once.
But...
Being upset because we might have had
the wrong idea is perhaps unreasonable.
However, this sense of betrayal
exceeds expectations.
We should make these gloomy feelings explode,
go up to the rooftop, and then we can fly!
Mari-chan! Mari-chan, Mari-chan, calm down!
And then they will travel to
the legendary yuri garden—
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
I lost control for a moment.
I might be more worried about
you than them, Mari-chan.
Yeah, but what's sad is really sad.
Aki-sama and our...
Destroy Men Instantly
...completely untainted...
...holy yuri kingdom.
Do you mind if I sit here?
You bastard!
You've got some nerve showing
your face around here!
Whoa!
That's quite the welcome.
Huh?
Very well. Take care of him, Kikune-san.
Got it.
Go!
Wait! Hang on!
You have the wrong idea!
The wrong idea?
Yes! Honest!
There's something that
I need to tell you all.
Heart Flutter Actions!
Heart Flutter Mannerisms!
Situations That Girls Love
Heart Flutter Special!!
We'll show you the results of our survey ranking!
1st Place: Wall Slam!
Hey, Masamune-kun. Are you listening?
Yasaka Festival Proposal Meeting
Let's talk about this seriously, okay?
Sorry, Class Rep.
Let's talk about our class's
project for the festival.
Our class's project, huh?
I got it! I, Futaba Tae, thought about this
until my brain became strained, then squishy!
We can have a play with the super cute
Kojuurou-kyun starring as Snow White,
and the super hot Masamune-kun as the prince!
That sounds lovely.
Um... Why am I the princess?
Let's do this, Class 2-B!
Yeah!
Give it up, Kojuurou. No one can fight this.
It always ends up this way...
Heart Flutter Special!!
I don't care if we have to act or sing.
What I have to do something
about is that bastard.
This is my chance! That fatty isn't here!
M-Makabe?!
What are you doing?
I figured we wouldn't be able to
have a real talk if I didn't do this.
There's nothing to talk about.
I have something to say!
Is that so?
All right, just one thing.
So close...
You're open down there.
Wait, what?!
Thank goodness, it's closed.
Huh? Adagaki-san?
Masa— I mean, Kanetsugu,
let's hurry up and go to class.
Sure.
That damn fatty again...
That was pointless!
The wall slam was powerless!
Completely powerless!
Makabe Masamune...
How dare he use the wall slam on Aki-sama?!
We can't let our guard down for a second.
Common sense doesn't work on beasts.
The choice we made is not wrong.
Let us protect Aki-sama.
Along with "him."
Something you need to tell us?
That's right.
Amazingly enough, I'm engaged to Aki-chan,
but I have no intention of furthering
our relationship beyond that at all.
What? So you're engaged to her,
but you don't even like her?
No! It's the exact opposite.
She's truly like some beautiful goddess,
so I don't have any right
to lay a finger on her.
Really? You're not going to kiss her? Ever?
Of course not! I know my place.
What should we do? That might
actually be pretty respectable.
He won't touch her because he likes her.
That's kind of cowardly. I don't like it.
But Aki-sama's purity will be protected,
far more than with Makabe Masamune.
No!
Makabe Masamune...
We won't let you have Aki-sama!
The beast must be destroyed.
Student Council Room
Aren't there quite a few requests
for the Yasaka Festival this year?
That's a good thing.
Good work, guys! Sorry I'm late.
Vice President, you've got work piled up.
Yup, I know.
Huh? This is insane!
What's the matter, Vice President?
The proposals from each class...
Both 2-A and 2-B want to
put on the play "Snow White."
So they both picked the same thing.
Then we should approve Class B,
since they turned in their proposal first.
No...
Cultural Festival Proposal Form
It should be Class A.
But...
It's gotta be A. Definitely A.
There's no other choice but A!
Cultural Festival Proposal Form
Please let us reevaluate this.
Yup, so it's Class A, right?
Student Council
Nothing less from the vice president,
the one pulling the strings
at Yasaka from the shadows.
Declined?
No way! We can't think of
something else at this point!
But we can't have two of the same thing.
Yeah, but why is it us?
Because the vice president was so insistent—
I mean, it was a student council decision.
What's wrong?
Apparently our proposal for the
Yasaka Festival was declined.
Huh? Just our class?
Whatever! We submitted ours first.
We just have to convince
Class A, right? I'll go.
What?
Why is she so passionate?
Passion may be strong enough to
blast away the unreasonable.
We refuse.
It has already been decided
that Class A will be performing
"Snow White" with Aki-sama and
Kanetsugu-sama as the leads.
Wh-What?!
We've already decided, too!
We're doing "Snow White" starring heartthrobs
Kojuurou-kyun and Masamune-kun!
Wh-What?!
Why don't you give up?
I'm sure there was a request to decline that.
I mean, a "Snow White" with
only men is nothing but futile.
C-Class Rep?
It's way weirder to have a fat prince!
Fat is a sign of wealth.
This isn't about what I want to do.
I just want to show the audience
what they want to see.
This was a unanimous decision in our class.
Now, now. Calm down, you two.
She was suddenly rejected.
We should consider how she feels.
W-Well, you're exactly right, Kanetsugu.
I guess I can see her point.
What the hell is with this Cruel
Princess? It's infuriating!
Then why don't we promote this by saying
we'll decide the winner by popular vote?
Masamune-kun...
Popular vote?
The best project is chosen by votes, right?
So doing the same play will actually
make it easier to determine a winner.
That's a great idea! A drama battle!
That'll hype things up for sure!
True... I guess I'd have to say that's fair.
I suppose it might be if
you say so, Aki-sama.
What do you think, student council?
We can promote both of them at once.
Well, if you both agree to this,
I believe it'll be okay.
Yes!
Then I believe this is now officially
a competition, Futaba-san.
Of course. We're not going
to lose, Adagaki-san!
Could we add on another competition?
Whoever wins gets to dance with
someone at the post-festival party.
I can't just sit here biting
my nails, Round Prince.
I guess it's pointless to ask with whom.
All right. I'm in.
All right!
There's no going back on this!